t-shirts.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy

Effective on date 03/17/2016

This privacy policy applies to [www.HalloweenCostumes.com](https://www.halloweencostumes.com/), [www.Shirts.com](http://www.shirts.com/) and [www.fun.com](https://www.fun.com/) owned and operated by Fun.com, Inc. This privacy policy describes how Shirts.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site [www.Shirts.com](https://www.halloweencostumes.com/), [www.Shirts.com](http://www.shirts.com/) and [www.fun.com](https://www.fun.com/) and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the website. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

Shirts.com has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed for compliance with the [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through these web sites: [www.HalloweenCostumes.com](https://www.halloweencostumes.com/), [www.Shirts.com](http://www.shirts.com/) and [www.fun.com](https://www.fun.com/).

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe [here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password

We also collect the following optional information from you:

  * Information about your business such as company name

We use this information to:

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates
  * Administer your account or process refunds
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Display content based upon your interests
  * List you in our member directory made available only to select employees

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

## Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can [contact us](http://www.shirts.com/contact-us.aspx).

## Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personal information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you want to remove your personal information that is being displayed on our website under public pages please send your request to our [contact form](http://www.shirts.com/contact-us.aspx).

## Information Obtained from Third Parties

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us. Your friend may contact us using our contact form to request that we remove this information from our database.

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Shirts.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

### Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider

Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Shirts.com and partners (Share-A-Sale; AvantLink; Google Analytics), affiliates, or analytics or service providers (Criteo; Bronto; Sales Force). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart to remember our user's settings (e.g. language preference) for our shopping cart and authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as Flash and HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118>

We Partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These Features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Shirts.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policy. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

 **Analytics**

Protecting Your Online Privacy. Our priority is to keep your online data safe. As part of our promise to you, we wanted to let you know that this website uses Google Analytics, Google Display Advertising, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to help us understand how visitors use our site. The tools mentioned above use "cookies," which are essentially text files placed on your computer to gather standard Internet log information and user behavior information in an anonymous form. The information created by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google and is then used to evaluate visitors' use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for our site specifically. 

We will never (nor will we allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personal Information of visitors to our website. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google, nor will Google link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personal Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.

If you would like to opt out of being tracked using Google Analytics on any website, then simply head over to [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and install the add-on in your browsers. 

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services please [contact us](http://www.shirts.com/contact-us.aspx). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce agreements.

## Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can [contact us](http://www.shirts.com/contact-us.aspx).

We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third party payment option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information (such as credit card information) collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose to use a third party payment option to pay for your order, its privacy policy and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy policy before providing your information.

## Additional Policy Information

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

Our Web site offers a publicly accessible blog or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access it. The blog is mediated and you may have comments made by yourself removed by [contacting us](http://www.shirts.com/contact-us.aspx).

Live chat option is available on our websites, which will allow you to communicate with our customer service representative. You will be asked to provide your Personal Information to initiate a chat. This information is only used by Shirts.com to assure proper quality control and will not be use for any other purpose than to provide the Live Chat service.

## Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information

To review, delete or update your personal information to ensure it is accurate or if you no longer desire our service, please [contact us](http://www.shirts.com/contact-us.aspx). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

## Notification of Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Contact Information

You can contact us by phone, mail or email:

Shirts.com  
2080 Lookout Drive  
North Mankato, MN 56003

Phone: (507) 386-8385 (Monday - Friday  
7 a.m. - 7 p.m. CST   
Saturday   
10 a.m. - 4 p.m.   
Sunday   
Closed.)

## California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

Under California law, our customers that are California residents may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As detailed above, we do not share our customer's personal information with unaffiliated third parties for direct marketing purposes without their approval.

If at any time you wish to opt out of having your personal information shared with third parties and/or receiving information from Shirts.com (via e-mail or postal mail) about new products, services, or promotions, you can do so. You can contact us by through our [contact form](http://www.shirts.com/contact-us.aspx). Please indicate what publications or services you no longer wish to receive so that we may better address your needs.
